so I just ordered coyotes this book the
illusion of money and when you preorder
it off of his website or just pre-order
it and then on the website you can put
in the receipt number and get access to
the documentary that he did the illusion
of money which I'm looking even more
forward to than the book because that's
just how my mind works I love movies I
love the spoken word my brain when it's
auditory and visual picks it up much
faster then it can no longer quite do
with reading like it used to be able to
do but that's not the point
I love Kyle ceases work I love 99% of
what he says and the one percent I don't
I know it's like my inner trigger it's
about me learning the rest but I do find
the self-help community in general and
this is not pertaining to Cal C's
because I think he actually kind of says
the opposite is that this obsession with
both health and money that like if
you're doing what is right that you will
be healthy and you will be rich and
money will find you and if that's not
happening and then like you're just not
using it right you're not using the
secret right you're not using positive
affirmations enough and the reason I
find that broken is that what I am here
to do is bigger than that if what I'm
here to learn is going through a health
challenge who I to say I'm not supposed
to be going through a health challenge
if what I'm here to learn is supposed to
be having a lack of monetary means in
the world so that I can create a world
for everybody with black of monetary
means where we solve it as a group and a
collective and we let money not have
this power over us collectively that it
currently does that is what I'm here to
do I can't do that if I've never
experienced property I wouldn't even
know how to do that I wouldn't know what
the experience is to be lacking in money
and I know that I am experiencing
exactly what I'm supposed to experience
in order to learn the lessons I am here
to learn to be my unique self to
contribute to the world and what I'm
here to do is huge and it involves
having huge obstacles to overcome and I
think we break the process by saying
that like you're doing it wrong if
you're in assess data that's why I'm
reading also the completion process
actually I'm reading it and I'm almost
done it and I love that there is no
wrong that there is no bad emotion
they're all here to teach you and I
would say the same is true for
experiences as somebody who stress is
detrimental to my life it's life or
death it decays my life it hurts my
nervous system that makes it sound like
I can't do anything and in fact I've had
to become way stronger than those people
just doesn't appear that way to the
outside I've had to de-stress like
logically de-stress and emotionally
distressed of the situations that bring
other people's stress interpersonal
relationships and stuff that used to
bring me social anxiety I've had to let
go of it release it it's a constant
process I've had to figure out how to
deal with sensory torture in a way that
like in a world where that's not allowed
you're not allowed to be tortured by
sound and smell and light continually
because you then you don't function and
so although it's still there and I have
to mitigate that my own life I also have
gotten a level of patience does not
appear to be outside world because I
also don't have a level of patience like
I lose my shame a lot because it's
overwhelming but to get to that
threshold and to constantly increase
that threshold is part of what I'm here
to learn and I just love that we all do
have our own path to learn and we can't
even judge our own let alone everybody
else's because I can see clearly why
I've been meant to go through every
single struggle in the past and
currently in order to be able to put
this global cooperative together and
create a world that works for everyone
in order to create a world that works
for everyone
the
had to on a fundamental level not work
for me so that my brain can be like but
what if it could what does that look
like if it worked for you because if it
works for me it works for almost
everybody because there's a lot of ways
my like it's hard to eat healthy and
well when you don't have the spoons and
you don't have the money so if I can
figure out a way to eat healthy for me
and my kid will eat it then that means
like basically everyone can get healthy
if it's a system that meets you where
you are that you don't have to increase
your money you don't have to increase
your energy and instead you can use what
you're currently using and money and
energy and get more and more and more
for it and I'm very blessed in my life
to have access to services and community
like to live in community where I get to
show up and eat four times a week and
not have to worry about cooking and
cleaning in and I get that nutrition in
my kid gets that nutrition without
having to worry about the energy that
went into it and I get to do that for
the community once a cycle and clean
once a cycle my clean is tomorrow it's
gotta save some smoothies for that so I
just wanted to come on and give my I'm
so excited to be watching this
documentary which I might be watching
this afternoon or tonight and I will do
a video on it I am sure maybe several
thank like and subscribe please